Guide to the Group Research, Inc. Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Topical Files
  - Van Fleet, James A. (Gen.), Washington, DC (Box 323)
    [Military advisor and right-wing activist associated with Life Line Foundation, Inc. and American Afro-Asian Educational Exchange, Inc. among others See also the Group Research directory under Gen. James A. Van Fleet.]
  - Van Gorder, Dan P. (Box 323)
  - Van Sickle, Tom (Box 323)
    [See also Young Republicans.]
  - Vantage Press, New York, NY (Box 323)
  - Varney, Harold Lord (Box 323)
    [President and Co-Founder, Committee on Pan-American Policy See also Allen A. Zoll, Committee on Pan-American Policy, and the Group Research directory under Harold Lord Varney.]
  - Venezuela (Box 324)
    [See also Defenders of American Liberties.]
  - Vennard, Wickliffe B. (Box 324)
  - "Verdict", New York, NY (Box 324)
  - Veritas Committee on Pacem in Terris, Godfrey, IL (Box 324)
  - Veritas Foundation, West Sayville, NY (Box 324)
  - Vernon Fund, Washington, DC (Box 324)
  - Veterans and Citizens Committee Against Communism (Box 324)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (VFW) "American Security Reporter" (Box 324)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (VFW), 1971- (Box 324)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (VFW) (Box 324)
    [See also Christ Anti-Communism Crusade and Series 3 -- Indiana.]
  - Veterans Industrial Association (Box 324)
  - Victor Publishing Company, Shepherdsville, KY and South Bend, IN (Box 324)
  - Victorian League of Rights, Melbourne, Victoria (Box 324)
  - Victory in Vietnam Association (VIVA) (Box 324)
  - Victory Only Through Education (VOTE), Los Angeles, CA (Box 325)
  - Viereck, George Sylvester (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- Clippings, 1970 (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- Clippings, 1968-9 (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- Clippings, 1967 (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- Clippings, 1966 (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- Clippings, 1965 (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- Clippings, 1963-4 (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- "Congressional Record" clippings (Box 325)
  - Vietnam -- General (Box 325)
    [See also Central Intelligence Agency (CIA).]
  - Vietnam -- Letters to Congressmen (Box 325)
  - Vietnam Gift PAC (Box 326)
  - Viewpoint Books, San Diego, CA (Box 326)
  - Viewpoint Educational Foundation, Encino, CA (Box 326)
  - Vigilantes (Box 326)
  - Viguerie, Richard A. 1980- (Box 326)
  - Viguerie, Richard A. 1976- (Box 326)
  - Viguerie, Richard A. (Box 326)
  - Virginia Commission on Constitutional Government (Box 327)
  - Virginia Committee for Economic Freedom (Box 327)
  - Virginia Conservative Council (Box 327)
  - Virginia Education Fund, Inc. Richmond, VA (Box 327)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Company (Box 327)
  - Virginia for Goldwater (Box 327)
  - Virginia League, The (Box 327)
  - Virtue Foundation, Philip and Tecia Virtue, P. M. Los Angeles, CA (Box 327)
    [See also teh Group Research directory under Philip and Tecia Virtue Foundation.]
  - Vision, Inc. Spokane, WA (Box 327)
  - Vision, Stroudsburg, PA (Box 327)
  - "Vision Letter, The" (Box 327)
  - Vital Issues Group of New York City, New York, NY (Box 327)
  - Vitamin Products Company, Milwaukee, WI (Box 327)
  - Vivas, Eliseo (Box 327)
  - Voelker Company, Henry R. Indianapolis, IN (Box 327)
  - "Voice for Victory" (Box 327)
  - "Voice of Cuba, The" (Box 327)
  - "Voice of Freedom", Dallas, TX (Box 327)
  - "Voice of Liberty, The", Decatur, GA (Box 327)
  - "Voice of New Orleans", New Orleans, LA (Box 327)
  - "Voice of Prophecy, The" (Box 327)
  - Voice of the Constitution, The, Reno, NV (Box 327)
  - Voice of the Nazarene (Box 327)
  - Voice of the People in Action (The Society of the People, Inc.), Chillum, MD (Box 327)
  - "Voice of Truth and Freedom, The", Anaheim, CA (Box 327)
  - Voice of Youth (Box 327)
    [See also Free Enterprise Institute.]
  - Voices in Vital America (VIVA) (Box 327)
  - Volker Fund, William, Burlingame, CA (Box 327)
    [See also the Group Research directory under William Volker Fund.]
  - Volunteer Committee on Dual Sovereignty (Box 328)
  - Volunteers, The, Alabama (Box 328)
  - Volunteers for Constitutional Government (Box 328)
  - Volunteers of America (Box 328)
  - Von Freelick, Gerri (Box 328)
  - Von Mises, Ludwig (Box 328)
    [Professor of Economics, University of Vienna and New York University See also William Volker Fund and the Group Research directory under Ludwig von Mises.]
  - Von Zell, Harry (Box 328)
    [Radio and television actor and announcer See also the Group Research directory under Harry Von Zell.]
  - Voronaeff, Paul (Box 328)
  - Voss, Earl (Box 328)
  - "Voter's Voice in Congress" (Box 328)
    [See also "Focus on Congress."]
  - Voting Records, 1972- (Box 328)
    [This file contains numerous cross-references to articles and other publications. See also the Group Research directory under Special Reports -- Voting Records and Indexes.]
  - Voting Rights (Box 328)
  - Vulture Bonanza, Wickenburg, AZ (Box 328)
  - WGCB (radio station), Red Lion, PA (Box 346)
  - Wabash College, Crawfordsville, IN (Box 328)
    [See also Liberty Fund, Inc. and "Principles of Freedom."]
  - Wackenhut Corporation (Box 328)
    [See also Bugging.]
  - "Wackenhut Security Review" (Box 328)
  - "Waco Farm and Labor Journal", Waco, TX (Box 329)
  - Wage Earners Committee of the U.S.A. (Box 329)
  - Waggoner, Joe D. (Dr.) (Box 329)
  - Wagner, Paul (Box 329)
    [DAR public relations consultant]
  - Wagner, Richard (Box 329)
  - Wagner, Walter (Box 329)
  - Waite, D. A. (Rev.) (Box 329)
  - Waite Lawsuit (Box 329)
    [Materials about Rev. D. Waite suing Group Research, Inc.]
  - Wake Up America! (Box 329)
  - Wake Up America Foundation (Box 329)
  - Waldeck, R. G. (Countess) (Box 329)
  - Walker, A. W. (Mrs.), Amarillo, TX (Box 329)
  - Walker, B. E. (Mrs.), Amarillo, TX (Box 329)
  - Walker, Edwin A. (Maj.Gen.) General (Box 329)
    [See this file for numerous cross-references.]
  - Walker, Edwin A. (Maj.Gen.) Magazine and "Congressional Record" clippings (Box 329)
  - Walker, Edwin A. (Maj.Gen.) Newspaper clippings (Box 329)
  - Walker, Edwin A. (Maj.Gen.) Newspaper clippings (Box 329)
  - Walker, Prentiss (Rep.), R-MS (Box 330)
  - Walker, Richard L. (Dr.), University of South Carolina, Columbia, SC (Box 330)
  - Wall, William M. (Monsignor), Paterson, NJ (Box 330)
  - Wall Street Journal (Box 330)
  - Wallace Detective Agency (Box 330)
  - Wallace, DeWitt (and Mrs.) (Box 330)
  - Wallace, Frank (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George AJS Report, 1968 (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George, 1976- (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George, 1975- (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George, 1972-4 (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George Party, 1970-2 (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George Electors -- official lists, 1968 (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George Party and Post election, 1968- (Box 330)
  - Wallace, George, January-June 1968 (Box 331)
  - Wallace, George, July-August 1968 (Box 331)
  - Wallace, George, September-December 1968 (Box 331)
  - Wallace, George Wallace for President, Alexandria, VA, 1968 (Box 331)
  - Wallace, George Youth for Wallace, 1968 (Box 331)
  - Wallace, George, 1967 (Box 331)
  - Wallace, George (Gov.), D-AL (Box 331)
    [See also Christian Nationalist Crusade.]
  - Wallou, George (Box 332)
  - Walt, Lewis W. (Gen.) (Box 332)
  - Walter, Bob (Pastor) (Box 332)
  - Walter, Francis B. (Rep.), D-PA (Box 332)
  - Walton, Izaak (Box 332)
  - Walton, Rus (Box 332)
  - "Wanderer, The", St. Paul, MN (Box 332)
    [See also the Group Research directory under "The Wanderer."]
  - War Control Planners, Inc. (Box 332)
  - "War/Peace Report" (Box 332)
  - Ward, Chester (Admiral), Washington, DC and Honolulu, HI (Box 332)
    [Speaker, specializing in Cold War seminars, and member of several right-wing organizations See also the Group Research directory under Admiral Chester Ward, under "Strike from Space" (a book by Ward and Phyllis Schlafly), and under "The Gravediggers" (another book by Ward and Phyllis Schlafly).]
  - Ward, J. L. (Rev.), Memphis, TN (Box 332)
  - Warner and Swasey, Cleveland, OH (Box 332)
  - Warner, Jack (Box 332)
  - Warner, Jerome R. NE (Box 332)
  - Warren Commission and Warren Report (Box 332)
    [See also Citizens Against Communism.]
  - Warren Impeachment, Earl Pro-Impeachment materials (Box 332)
  - Washington Exclusive (Box 332)
    [See also U.S. Press Association.]
  - "Washington Independent", Washington, DC (Box 332)
  - Washington Institute for Values in Public Policy, The, Washington, DC (Box 332)
  - Washington Journalism Center, Inc. Washington, DC (Box 332)
  - Washington Legal Foundation, Washington, DC, 1986- (Box 332)
  - Washington Legal Foundation, Washington, DC (Box 332)
  - Washington Memorial Foundation, George, Cleveland, OH (Box 332)
  - "Washington News Beat", Washington, DC (Box 333)
  - Washington News Service, Washington, DC (Box 333)
  - "Washington Notebook", Yonkers, NY (Box 333)
  - "Washington Observer", Torrance, CA (Box 333)
  - Washington Researchers, Washington, DC (Box 333)
  - Washington Summary, Seattle, WA (Box 333)
  - "Washington Times, The", Washington, DC (Box 333)
  - Washington Workshops, Washington, DC (Box 333)
  - Washington World (Box 333)
  - Watch and Pray, Los Angeles, CA (Box 333)
  - Watch Washington Club Griffiths, Warren (Mrs.), Columbus, OH (Box 333)
    [President of the Watch Washington Club]
  - Watergate, 1992- (Box 333)
    [See also Series 2 -- Richard Nixon -- Watergate.]
  - Waters, Agnes (Box 333)
  - Watson, Albert W. (Rep.), R-SC (Box 333)
  - Watson, Tom (Box 333)
  - Watson, W. Marvin (Box 333)
  - Watt, James G. (Box 333)
  - Watts, Blaine, Midvale, UT (Box 333)
  - Watts, Clyde J. (Box 333)
    [See also Edwin Walker and Military Muzzling.]
  - Watts, Robert B. (Dr.) (Box 333)
  - Watts, Vernon Orval (Box 333)
  - Wayne, John, Beverly Hills, CA (Box 333)
    [Actor See also the Group Research directory under John Wayne.]
  - We Love America (Box 333)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1969 (Box 333)
    [See also the Group Research directory under We, The People!]
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box 333)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1967 (Box 333)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1966 (Box 333)
  - We, The People! Materials distributed at convention, Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1966 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1965 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Materials distributed at convention, Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1965 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1964 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1963 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1962 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1961 (Box 334)
    [See also Audio/Visual box.]
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1960 (Box 334)
  - We, The People! Headquarters in Chicago, IL, 1955-9 (Box 334)
  - Weaver, Richard M. (Dr.) (Box 334)
  - Webb, James (Box 334)
  - Wedemeyer, Albert C. (Gen.), Washington, DC (Box 334)
    [War veteran, author, and right-wing activist See also the Group Research directory under Gen. Albert C. Wedemeyer.]
  - "Weekly Bulletin, The", Largo, FL (Box 334)
  - "Weekly Crusader, The", Tulsa, OK (Box 334)
  - Weekly Labor Forecast and Review (Box 334)
    [See also State Labor News.]
  - Weeks, Elizabeth, Los Angeles, CA (Box 334)
  - Weidenbaum, Murray L. (Box 334)
  - Weinberger, Caspar W. (Box 334)
  - Weissman, Bernard (Box 334)
  - Welch, Herbert (Bishop) (Box 334)
  - Welch, Vincent B. (Box 334)
  - Welcome Wagon (Box 334)
  - Welfare (Box 334)
    [See also Poverty Program and Joseph Mitchell.]
  - Welfare Pressure Groups (Box 334)
  - Welk, Lawrence (Box 334)
  - Wells, Kenneth D. Valley Forge, PA (Box 334)
    [Co-Founder and Former President, Freedoms Foundation See also Daughters of the American Revolution (DAR), Freedoms Foundation, and the Group Research directory under Kenneth D. Wells.]
  - "Wells Newsletter" (Box 334)
  - Werner, Edward H. Hicksville, NY (Box 334)
  - West, Dick, Dallas, TX (Box 334)
  - "Westchester Conservative, The", Armonk, NY (Box 335)
  - Westerfield, Pat (Box 335)
  - "Western Destiny", Los Angeles, CA (Box 335)
    [Published by Noontide Press See also the Group Research directory under "Western Destiny."]
  - Western Foundation, The (Box 335)
  - Western Front, Hollywood, CA (Box 335)
  - Western Gear Corporation (Box 335)
  - Western Goals Foundation (Box 335)
  - Western Hemisphere's Directorate, Philadelphia, PA (Box 335)
  - Western Messenger, Riverside, CA (Box 335)
  - Western Research Foundation (Box 335)
  - Western Research Library (Box 335)
  - Western Tax Council, Chicago, IL (Box 335)
  - "Western Voice", Englewood, CO (Box 335)
  - Western Women Civilaires (Box 335)
  - Western Wood Products Association, Portland, OR (Box 335)
  - Westin, Alan F. New York, NY (Box 335)
    [Professor of Public Law, Columbia University See also National Civil Liberties Clearing House.]
  - Westminster Academy (Box 335)
  - Westmoreland, William C. (Gen.) (Box 335)
  - Weston, Joseph H. Salt Lake City, UT (Box 335)
    [See also James A. Van Fleet.]
  - Westside Developers, Inc. (Box 335)
  - Weyl, Nathaniel (Box 335)
  - Whalen, Richard (Box 336)
  - Whaley-Eaton Service, Washington, DC (Box 336)
  - Wheat Sale to Russia (Box 336)
  - Wheaton College, Wheaton, IL (Box 336)
  - Wheeler, Burton K. (Box 336)
  - "While Brave Men Die" (film) (Box 336)
    [See also Newscope.]
  - Whinery, John G. Amarillo, TX (Box 336)
  - Whitaker and Baxter (Box 336)
    [Public Relations firm. See also Citizens Committee for Balanced Representation and Reapportionment.]
  - White, Bob, MN (Box 336)
    [Columnist See also Minneapolis Daily American.]
  - White Book Store (Box 336)
  - White Circle League of America, Chicago, IL (Box 336)
    [See also Black Muslims.]
  - White Crusaders (Box 336)
  - White, Frederick Clifton (Box 336)
  - White Horse Crusade, Los Angeles, CA (Box 336)
  - White Legion Books, Silver Spring, MD (Box 336)
  - White Muslim Religion, The, Berkley, MI (Box 336)
  - White, Natalie (Box 336)
  - White, Opal Tanner, Los Angeles, CA (Box 336)
    [Former Chairman, Citizens Congressional Committee See also the Group Research directory under Opal Tanner White.]
  - White Panthers (Box 336)
  - White Party of America, Washington, DC (Box 336)
    [See also George Wallace.]
  - White Peoples Party, The, Metairie, LA (Box 336)
  - "White Sentinel, The", Ft. Lauderdale, FL (Box 336)
    [See also American Birthright Committee.]
  - White Supremacy (Box 336)
  - White, Thomas D. (Gen.) (Box 336)
  - White, W. L. (Box 336)
  - White, William S. (Box 336)
  - Whittaker, Charles E. (Box 336)
  - Whitworth College, Brookhaven, MS (Box 336)
  - Who's Who Clubs of America (Box 336)
    [See also the Associated Clubs, Inc.]
  - "Who's Who International" (Box 336)
  - Wichita Collegiate School, Wichita, KS (Box 336)
  - Wick, Chad (Box 336)
  - Wickham, Don J. (Box 336)
  - Wide Awake Anti-Communism Crusade (Box 336)
    [See also Betty McConkey and the Group Research directory under "Communism's Plan for Agriculture in America."]
  - Widener, Alice, New York, NY (Box 336)
    [Author and columnist Founder, "USA" (magazine) See also the Group Research directory under Alice Widener and "USA" (magazine).]
  - Wiegand, Edwin L. (Box 336)
  - Wiegand Foundation, Edwin L and Ann K. (Box 336)
  - Wiegand, G. C. (Dr.), Carbondale, IL (Box 336)
    [Professor of Economics, Southern Illinois University.]
  - Wiggins, James W. (Box 336)
  - Wilcox, Edward Barkley (Box 336)
  - Wilcox, Laird (Box 336)
  - Wilder, L. Douglas (Gov.), D-VA (Box 337)
  - Wilken, Carl H. (Box 337)
  - Wilkie Brothers Foundation, The, Des Plaines, IL (Box 337)
  - Wilkinson, Bud (Box 337)
  - Wilkinson, Ernest L. Provo, UT (Box 337)
    [President Brigham Young University. See also George Benson.]
  - Will, George (Box 337)
  - Williams, F. J. (Dr.), San Gabriel, CA (Box 337)
  - Williams, George C. Gatesville, TX (Box 337)
    [Associated with the Information Research Bureau.]
  - Williams, Hugh, Brooklyn, NY (Box 337)
  - Williams Intelligence Survey (Box 337)
  - Williams, J. Harvie (Box 337)
  - Williams, John Bell (Rep.), D-MS (Box 337)
  - Williams, Robert (Box 337)
  - Williams, Walter (Box 337)
  - Willis, Alan R. Spartanburg, SC (Box 337)
  - Willis Books, Fort Worth, TX (Box 337)
  - Willis, Harold R. Golden, CO (Box 337)
  - Willmouth, R. W. (Box 337)
  - Willoughby, Charles (Maj.Gen.), Washington, DC (Box 337)
    [Former aide to General MacArthur See also the Group Research directory under Maj.Gen. Charles Willoughby.]
  - Wills, Garry (Box 337)
    [Author and columnist.]
  - Wilson, Robert C. "Bob" (Rep.), R-CA (Box 337)
  - Wilson, Earl (Box 337)
  - Wilson, Eleanor M. (Box 337)
    [Assistant editor of "The Freedom Press."]
  - Wilson, Eugene E. (Box 337)
  - Wilson, George H. (Box 337)
  - Wilson, Jack R. W. Stockton, CA (Box 337)
  - Wilson, John (Box 337)
    [See also Constitution Party.]
  - Wilson, Lyle C. (Box 337)
    [See also the Goldwater Campaign.]
  - Wilson, Richard (Box 337)
  - Winchell, Walter (Box 337)
  - Winchester Foundation, Winchester, IN (Box 337)
  - Winds of Freedom Foundation, CA (Box 337)
  - Winegarten, Ruth (Mrs. Alvin) (Box 337)
    [See also National Write Your Congressman Club.]
  - Wings of Healing, Portland, OR (Box 337)
    [See also Student Statesman and Crusade for God and Freedom.]
  - Winona Lake Christian Assembly, Inc. Winona Lake, IN (Box 337)
  - Winpac, Bozeman, MT (Box 337)
  - Winrod, Gerald B. and Gordon (Box 337)
  - "Winrod Letter, The" Winrod, Gordon (editor) (Box 337)
  - Winter, William, Sausalito, CA (Box 337)
  - Wire Magazine (Box 337)
  - Wisconsin Conservative Club (Box 338)
  - Wisconsin Legislative and Research Committee, Inc. Brookfield, WI (Box 338)
  - Wise-Use Movement (Box 338)
  - "Witness, The", Dubuque, IA (Box 338)
  - Wittenberg Motor Company, Midway, WA (Box 338)
  - Wittmer, Felix (Box 338)
  - Wolff, Charles E. (Prof.) (Box 338)
  - Wolman, Leo (Dr.), New York, NY (Box 338)
    [Professor of Economics, Columbia University.]
  - Woman-Power, Asheville, NC (Box 338)
  - Woman's Christian Temperance Union (WCTU) (Box 338)
  - Woman's Right to Know, Inc. Lakeland, FL (Box 338)
  - Women Descendants of the Ancient and Honorable Artillery Company (Box 338)
  - Women for Constitutional Government (Box 338)
  - Women for God and Country, Youngstown, OH (Box 338)
  - Women Investors' Research Institute, Inc. Washington, DC (Box 338)
  - Women Mobilized for Change (Box 338)
  - Women on the Watch (WOW) (Box 338)
  - Women's Chamber of Commerce (Box 338)
  - Women's Crusade for a Common Sense Economy (Box 338)
  - Women's Draft Goldwater Committee (Box 338)
  - Women's Forum on National Security (Box 338)
  - Women's National Republican Campaign Committee (Box 338)
  - Women's Organization for Right to Work (Box 338)
    [See also Series 2 -- National Right to Work Committee.]
  - Women's Patriotic Conference on National Defense (Box 338)
  - Women Strike for Peace Women's Strike for Peace (Box 338)
  - "Women's Voice", Chicago, IL (Box 338)
  - Wood, John A. (Box 338)
    [See also Series 1 and 2 -- Liberty Lobby.]
  - Wood, Robert E. (Gen.), Chicago, IL (Box 338)
    [Right-wing activist associated with America First Committee, America's Future, Inc., and Campaign for the 48 States among others. See also the Buchanan Hearings and the H. L. Hunt Foundation.]
  - Wood, William H. (Box 338)
    [See also National Research Bureau, Inc.]
  - Woods, Dalton J. LA (Box 338)
  - Woodward, W. W. (Box 338)
    [Author]
  - Woodworth, R. T. (Rev.), Baltimore, MD (Box 338)
  - Woolery, Charles E. Littleton, CO (Box 338)
  - Woolley, Frank K. Chicago, IL (Box 338)
    [Staff, American Farm Bureau Federation and the American Medical Association (AMA) See also Americans for Constitutional Action, American Farm Bureau Federation, and the American Medical Association (AMA) as well as the Group Research directory under Frank K. Woolley.]
  - Word of Life, Inc. New York (Box 338)
  - "Worker, The", New York, NY (Box 338)
  - Workman, William D., Jr. (Box 338)
  - "World, The" (Box 338)
  - World Anti-Communist League, 1987- (Box 339)
  - World Anti-Communist League (Box 339)
  - World Committee for a World Constitutional Convention (Box 339)
  - World Freedom Foundation (Box 339)
  - World News Institute (Box 339)
  - World Peace Broadcasting Foundation (Box 339)
  - World Press Institute (Box 339)
  - World Service (Box 339)
  - World Tapes for Education, Dallas, TX (Box 339)
  - World-Truth (Box 339)
  - World Veterans Fund, Inc. (Box 339)
  - World Vision, Inc. (Box 339)
  - World-Wide Missions (Box 339)
  - Wormser, Felix Edgar (Box 339)
  - Wormser, Rene A. (Box 339)
    [See also the Group Research directory under "Foundations: Their Power and Influence" (a book by Wormser).]
  - Worrell, Margaret Hopkins, Washington, DC (Box 339)
  - Worthy, William W. (Box 339)
    [Writer and lecturer]
  - Wright, David McCord, Athens, GA (Box 339)
    [Professor of Economics, University of Georgia]
  - Wright Foundation of Badger Meter, Inc. Milwaukee, WI (Box 339)
  - Wright, Hamilton, Sr. (Box 339)
  - Wright, Hardy E. (Box 339)
  - Wright, James C. "Jim" (Rep.), D-TX (Box 339)
  - Wright, Loyd, Los Angeles, CA (Box 339)
    [Attorney and right-wing activist See also the Group Research directory under Loyd Wright.]
  - Wrought Washer Foundation, Inc. Milwaukee, WI (Box 339)
  - Wurmbrand, Richard (Rev.), Glendale, CA (Box 339)
    [Founder, Jesus to the Communist World See also the Group Research directory under Rev. Richard Wurmbrand.]
  - Wyman, Louis C. (Rep.), R-NH (Box 339)
    [See also the Group Research directory under Louis C. Wyman.]
  - Xerox Company (Box 340)
    [See also Labor Educational Association and United Nations.]
  - Yakima National Security Seminar (Box 340)
  - Yarmolinsky, Adam (Box 340)
    [Aide to Robert S. McNamara, former Secretary of Defense]
  - Yarnall Associates, Polly A. Valley Forge, PA (Box 346)
    [See also The Long House, Inc.]
  - Yearling, Ervin Freeman (Rev.) (Box 340)
  - Yergan, Max (Dr.) (Box 340)
    [Former Chairman, American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters See also American Committee for Aid to Katanga Freedom Fighters.]
  - Yockey, Francis Parker (Box 340)
    [Author of Imperium and neo-Nazi sympathesizer Pseudonym, Ulick Varange See also the Group Research directory under Francis Parker Yockey and "Imperium."]
  - Yorty, Sam (Mayor), Los Angeles, CA (Box 340)
  - "You S. A.", Chicago, IL (Box 340)
  - Young American Enterprises, Los Angeles, CA (Box 340)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Magazine and "Congressional Record" clippings, Headquarters in Washington, DC (Box 340)
    [See also the Group Research directory under "The New Guard" (a monthly magazine published by YAF).]
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Newspaper clippings, Headquarters in Washington, DC, 1972- (Box 340)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Newspaper clippings, Headquarters in Washington, DC, 1970-1 (Box 340)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Newspaper clippings, Headquarters in Washington, DC (Box 340)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Letters and memos from National Headquarters, Headquarters in Washington, DC (Box 341)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Letters and materials from local and regional organizations, Headquarters in Washington, DC (Box 341)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Miscellaneous, Headquarters in Washington, DC (Box 341)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Miscellaneous, Headquarters in Washington, DC, 1991- (Box 341)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Miscellaneous, Headquarters in Washington, DC, 1976- (Box 342)
  - Young Americans for Freedom (YAF) Miscellaneous, Headquarters in Washington, DC, 1972-5 (Box 342)